## Vo Minh Hieu

### Software developer

+84978515919 | hieuvominh56@gmail.com | 591 Street 51 Bien Hoa City Dong Nai Viet Nam



## **Summary**

An opportunity to work and upgrade oneself, as well as being involved in an organization that believes in gaining a competitive edge and giving back to the community. I'm presently expanding my experience in application development. I focus on using my interpersonal skills to build good performance, data structures and algorithms, user experience for the application. I hope to develop skills in motion design and my knowledge of the System, and become a partner with you to build a best system. I'm self-confident you'll find me creative, funny and naturally passionate. I'm a forward thinker, which others may find inspiring when working as a team.

#### Skill & Abilities

- Back-end Related with some language like Ruby, Java, C++, .Net
- Front-end I can work with Javascript and use some JS Framework like Angular Js, React Js.
- Database I have experience with SQL server, MySQL, Mongo db, Elasticsearch, Sqlite, ...
- Data structures and Algorithms I have some pretty skills in algorithms.
- Agile I am experienced in Agile.

### Experience

Associate Software Engineer, DXC Technology, Ho Chi Minh City

09/2017 - 03/2019

I join Fresher Program at DXC in 9/2017 and passed. After that I join to the MISR team, an insurance outsourcing for an Egypt client. I work as front-end developer in MISR to 05/2018, then I change to mobility team in 1 month, after that I back to the web team and work as full stack developer.

Software Engineer, Deliveree On-Demand Logistics, Ho Chi Minh City

03/2019 - 04/2019

Deliveree is a logistics company on shipping service, I just work on Deliveree nearly 2 months and work as full stack developer.

After leave Deliveree, I join Hubble a startup to help construction companies manage their project and resource. I'm onboarding with Hubble when they are starting to build a team at HCMC.

When I just start working at Hubble, the time Vietnam team starting to build a new project to help construction companies can manage safety and quality of their workers. After done that I join the 'Workforces team' till today, my main role is as a frontend engineer to implement and maintain the whole system.

#### Education

Computer science, HCMC Open university, Ho Chi Minh City

05/2013 - 03/2018

# Hobby

- Reading book/blog/news about technical.
- I can sing very well. Let's sing a song  $\odot$ .
- Play video games if I have free time.
- I very love to learn new things or discuss about technical
- Board game.
- Planted aquarium.